(this["webpackJsonpreact-quiz"]=this["webpackJsonpreact-quiz"]||[]).push([[0],{11:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('{"data":[{"question":"1.Interacting with people makes me feel good. ?","choices":["Agree","Disagree"],"answer":"Agree"},{"question":"2.My goals in life are clear ?","choices":["Agree","Disagree"],"answer":"Agree"},{"question":"3.If people are rude to me I just shrug it off ?","choices":["Agree","Disagree"],"answer":"Disagree"},{"question":"4.I am confident in what I do ?","choices":["Agree","Disagree"],"answer":"Agree"},{"question":"5.I can work even when things are disorganized ?","choices":["Agree","Disagree"],"answer":"Disagree"},{"question":"6.I consistently put full time and effort into everything I do?","choices":["Agree","Disagree"],"answer":"Agree"},{"question":"7.I prefer achieving my goals than assisting others to achieve their goals?","choices":["Agree","Disagree"],"answer":"Disagree"},{"question":"8.I would describe myself as an extremely competent person?","choices":["Agree","Disagree"],"answer":"Disagree"},{"question":"9.I prefer working within a stable rather than flexible environment ?","choices":["Agree","Disagree"],"answer":"Disagree"},{"question":"10.I am ambitious ?","choices":["Agree","Disagree"],"answer":"Agree"},{"question":"11.It\'s better to get a job done than aim for perfection ?","choices":["Agree","Disagree"],"answer":"Disagree"},{"question":"12.I am able to complete tasks as well as, or better than other people ?","choices":["Agree","Disagree"],"answer":"Agree"},{"question":"13.I like to be in charge of other people ?","choices":["Agree","Disagree"],"answer":"Disagree"},{"question":"14.I strive to do the best I can ?","choices":["Agree","Disagree"],"answer":"Agree"},{"question":"15.I feel uneasy if I\'m the centre of attention?","choices":["Agree","Disagree"],"answer":"Disagree"},{"question":"16.I am confident in my abilities to complete difficult tasks at work ?","choices":["Agree","Disagree"],"answer":"Agree"},{"question":"17.I am happy to make speeches in public ?","choices":["Agree","Disagree"],"answer":"Disagree"},{"question":"18.It is very important for me to achieve my goals ?","choices":["Agree","Disagree"],"answer":"Agree"},{"question":"19.I like to react to things on the spur of the moment ?","choices":["Agree","Disagree"],"answer":"Disagree"},{"question":"20.I believe I am more intelligent than most ?","choices":["Agree","Disagree"],"answer":"Disagree"},{"question":"21.I don\'t like unexpected responsibilities?","choices":["Agree","Disagree"],"answer":"Disagree"},{"question":"22.I approach life in an easy-going manner?","choices":["Agree","Disagree"],"answer":"Agree"},{"question":"23.I tend to take on other people\u2019s problems?","choices":["Agree","Disagree"],"answer":"Disagree"},{"question":"24.I like to have plenty of time to myself?","choices":["Agree","Disagree"],"answer":"Agree"},{"question":"25.People often comment on how comfortable I am in giving orders?","choices":["Agree","Disagree"],"answer":"Disagree"},{"question":"26.I can solve my issues within time.?","choices":["Agree","Disagree"],"answer":"Disagree"},{"question":"27.I am flexible to work after office hours?","choices":["Agree","Disagree"],"answer":"Agree"},{"question":"28.Changes in my work makes me feel uncomfortable?","choices":["Agree","Disagree"],"answer":"Disagree"},{"question":"29.I almost cross deadline of work when there is work pressure?","choices":["Agree","Disagree"],"answer":"Agree"},{"question":"30.I am keen or specific about time management?","choices":["Agree","Disagree"],"answer":"Agree"},{"question":"31.I like to document, whatever is discussed with clients.?","choices":["Agree","Disagree"],"answer":"Agree"},{"question":"32.I have leadership qualities?","choices":["Agree","Disagree"],"answer":"Agree"}]}')},37:function(e,s,t){},61:function(e,s,t){"use strict";t.r(s);var n=t(1),a=t(0),i=t.n(a),r=t(6),c=t.n(r),o=t(4),l=(t(37),function(e){e.setName;var s=e.onQuizStart;return Object(n.jsx)("div",{className:"card",children:Object(n.jsx)("div",{className:"card-content",children:Object(n.jsxs)("div",{className:"content",children:[Object(n.jsx)("h1",{children:"Start the quiz"}),Object(n.jsx)("p",{children:"Good luck!"}),Object(n.jsx)("button",{className:"button is-info is-medium",onClick:s,children:"Start"})]})})})}),u=t(30),h=function(e){var s=e.data,t=e.onAnswerUpdate,i=e.numberOfQuestions,r=e.activeQuestion,c=e.onSetActiveQuestion,l=e.onSetStep,h=Object(a.useState)(""),g=Object(o.a)(h,2),d=g[0],j=g[1],b=Object(a.useState)(""),m=Object(o.a)(b,2),f=m[0],w=m[1],O=Object(a.useRef)();Object(a.useEffect)((function(){var e=O.current.querySelector("input:checked");e&&(e.checked=!1)}),[s]);var p=function(e){j(e.target.value),f&&w("")};return Object(n.jsx)("div",{className:"card",children:Object(n.jsx)("div",{className:"card-content",children:Object(n.jsxs)("div",{className:"content",children:[Object(n.jsx)("h2",{className:"mb-5",children:s.question}),Object(n.jsx)("div",{className:"control",ref:O,children:s.choices.map((function(e,s){return Object(n.jsxs)("label",{className:"radio has-background-light",children:[Object(n.jsx)("input",{type:"radio",name:"answer",value:e,onChange:p}),e]},s)}))}),f&&Object(n.jsx)("div",{className:"has-text-danger",children:f}),Object(n.jsx)("button",{className:"button is-link is-medium is-fullwidth mt-4",onClick:function(e){if(""===d)return w("Please select one option!");t((function(e){return[].concat(Object(u.a)(e),[{q:s.question,a:d}])})),j(""),r<i-1?c(r+1):l(3)},children:"Next"})]})})})},g=t(76),d=t(25),j=t.n(d),b=function(e){var s=e.results,t=e.data,i=e.onReset,r=e.onAnswersCheck,c=(e.time,Object(a.useState)(0)),l=Object(o.a)(c,2),u=l[0],h=l[1];return Object(a.useEffect)((function(){var e=0;s.forEach((function(s,n){s.a===t[n].answer&&e++})),h(e)}),[]),Object(n.jsx)("div",{className:"card",children:Object(n.jsx)("div",{className:"card-content",children:Object(n.jsxs)("div",{className:"content",children:[Object(n.jsx)("h3",{children:"Your results"}),Object(n.jsxs)("p",{children:[u," of ",t.length]}),Object(n.jsx)("p",{children:Object(n.jsxs)("strong",{children:[Math.floor(u/t.length*100),"%"]})}),Object(n.jsx)("button",{className:"button is-info mr-2",onClick:r,children:"Check your answers"}),Object(n.jsx)("button",{className:"button is-success",onClick:i,children:"Try again"}),Object(n.jsx)("button",{className:"button is-success",onClick:function(){j.a.post("../../score",s).then((function(e){console.log(e),window.location="/"}))},children:"Submit"}),Object(n.jsx)(g.a,{variant:"contained",color:"secondary",size:"large",style:{alignSelf:"center",marginTop:20},href:"/",children:"Go to homepage"})]})})})},m=function(e){var s=e.onClose,t=e.results,a=e.data;return Object(n.jsxs)("div",{className:"modal is-active",children:[Object(n.jsx)("div",{className:"modal-background",onClick:s}),Object(n.jsxs)("div",{className:"modal-card",children:[Object(n.jsxs)("header",{className:"modal-card-head",children:[Object(n.jsx)("p",{className:"modal-card-title",children:"Your answers"}),Object(n.jsx)("button",{className:"delete",onClick:s})]}),Object(n.jsx)("section",{className:"modal-card-body content",children:Object(n.jsx)("ul",{children:t.map((function(e,s){return Object(n.jsxs)("li",{className:"mb-6",children:[Object(n.jsx)("p",{children:Object(n.jsx)("strong",{children:e.q})}),Object(n.jsxs)("p",{className:e.a===a[s].answer?"has-background-success has-text-white p-2":"has-background-danger has-text-white p-2",children:["Your answer: ",e.a]}),e.a!==a[s].answer&&Object(n.jsxs)("p",{className:"has-background-link has-text-white p-2",children:["Correct answer: ",a[s].answer]})]},s)}))})})]})]})},f=t(11),w=function(){var e=Object(a.useState)(1),s=Object(o.a)(e,2),t=s[0],i=s[1],r=Object(a.useState)(0),c=Object(o.a)(r,2),u=c[0],g=c[1],d=Object(a.useState)([]),j=Object(o.a)(d,2),w=j[0],O=j[1],p=Object(a.useState)(!1),x=Object(o.a)(p,2),A=x[0],D=x[1];Object(a.useEffect)((function(){3===t&&clearInterval(undefined)}),[t]);return Object(n.jsxs)("div",{className:"App",children:[1===t&&Object(n.jsx)(l,{onQuizStart:function(){i(2)}}),2===t&&Object(n.jsx)(h,{data:f.data[u],onAnswerUpdate:O,numberOfQuestions:f.data.length,activeQuestion:u,onSetActiveQuestion:g,onSetStep:i}),3===t&&Object(n.jsx)(b,{results:w,data:f.data,onReset:function(){g(0),O([]),i(2)},onAnswersCheck:function(){return D(!0)}}),A&&Object(n.jsx)(m,{onClose:function(){return D(!1)},results:w,data:f.data})]})},O=function(e){e&&e instanceof Function&&t.e(3).then(t.bind(null,77)).then((function(s){var t=s.getCLS,n=s.getFID,a=s.getFCP,i=s.getLCP,r=s.getTTFB;t(e),n(e),a(e),i(e),r(e)}))};t(60);c.a.render(Object(n.jsx)(i.a.StrictMode,{children:Object(n.jsx)(w,{})}),document.getElementById("root")),O()}},[[61,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.6b8c5e26.chunk.js.map